http://www.batterysupplier.com/terms_privacy.asp

Your PrivacyYour
privacy is important to us. We collect only the information that is
necessary to process your order and notify you of any changes to your
order.  We do not sell your information to any List Services. A real person reviews each order before shipping.Security We Have a Valid Digital CertificateThis
means our website is authenticated with the use of a Volusion Secure
Site SSL Web Server Certificates to offer secure communications by encrypting all
data to and from the site. Volusion Secure Site SSL has checked and
verified our company registration documents and our site's registered
domain name. This information is included in the SSL certificate that
was issued to AGT Battery Supply. It verifies who we are, where we are
located, and that we are authorized to use our domain name. Note: SSL
is not active all the time while browsing a website. However SSL secure
mode is started when sensitive information is requested, such as a
credit card number. You'll find the Digital Certificate on the left margin. We ask you for the credit card CID or CVV2 number.
This is a four digit number on the front of the American Express Card
or the last 3 digits of the number on the back signature section of your
VISA or MasterCard. This is requested to prevent fraud. It helps to
verify that your credit card is physically in your possession.What Information We Need For Taking Your Order  When
you order from AGT Battery Supply, LLC there are a few things we
collect from you that you should be aware of. We do capture cookies in
order for us to keep track of the items you place in your shopping cart.
The "cookie" itself does not tell us who you are, your email address or
any other personal information about you. It merely allows us to keep
track of items in your shopping cart so you can move around the site
freely.All
other information we collect from you is given by you for the
completion of the order. This includes contact information (billing and
shipping addresses, phone number, email address), and financial
information (credit card).Your Email Address We
ask for your email address during the order so that we can send you a
shipping confirmation. We can also email you any changes to your order
that may effect timing or availability of items.  We do not send
countless mass email advertisements. We may send an occasional email
advertisement. Please inform us if you do not wish to receive email
advertisements.Your Address We
require your billing address, where your Credit Card Statement is
mailed to. This helps prevent fraud and allows us to confirm that your
order was authorized by you. We may mail you our catalogs and sale
promotions. If you do not wish to receive mailings please phone 800-340-3900 or send us an email. Tell us your customer number which you can find on the first line of the mailing label addressed to you. This Website www.agtbattery.com is owned and operated by AGT Battery Supply, LLCWe also own and operate the following domain names:www.Batterysupplier.comwww.agtbatteries.comwww.Batery.comwww.BatteryBattery.comwww.Motorola-Radio-Accessories.comYou may email us at: atessmer@agtbattery.comYou may phone us at: 1.800-340-3900 or 973-781-1100What information do we collect?We collect information from you when you register on the site, place an order, enter a contest or sweepstakes, respond to a survey or communication such as e-mail, or participate in another site feature.When ordering or registering, we may ask you for your name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information or other information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.We also collect information about gift recipients so that we can fulfill the gift purchase. The information we collect about gift recipients is not used for marketing purposes.Like many websites, we use "cookies" to enhance your experience and gather information about visitors and visits to our websites. Please refer to the "Do we use 'cookies'?" section below for information about cookies and how we use them.How do we use your information?We may use the information we collect from you when you register, purchase products, enter a contest or promotion, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:To personalize your site experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.To quickly process your transactions.To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.If you have opted-in to receive our e-mail newsletter, we may send you periodic e-mails. If you would no longer like to receive promotional e-mail from us, please refer to the "How can you opt-out, remove or modify information you have provided to us?" section below. If you have not opted-in to receive e-mail newsletters, you will not receive these e-mails. Visitors who register or participate in other site features such as marketing programs and 'members-only' content will be given a choice whether they would like to be on our e-mail list and receive e-mail communications from us.How do we protect visitor information?We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information. Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. When you place orders or access your personal information, we offer the use of a secure server. All sensitive/credit information you supply is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our databases to be only accessed as stated above.Do we use "cookies"?Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Netscape Navigator or Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. If you turn cookies off, you won't have access to many features that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly. However, you can still place orders over the telephone by contacting customer service.Do we disclose the information we collect to outside parties?We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information unless we provide you with advance notice, except as described below. The term "outside parties" does not include www.agtbattery.com. It also does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety.However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.How can you opt-out, remove or modify information you have provided to us?To modify your e-mail subscriptions, please let us know by modifying your preferences in the "My Account" section. Please note that due to email production schedules you may receive any emails already in production.To delete all of your online account information from our database, sign into the "My Account" section of our site and remove your shipping addresses, billing addresses & payment information. Please note that we may maintain information about an individual sales transaction in order to service that transaction and for record keeping.Third party linksIn an attempt to provide you with increased value, we may include third party links on our site. These linked sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these linked sites (including if a specific link does not work).Changes to our policyIf we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. Policy changes will apply only to information collected after the date of the change. This policy was last modified on August 6, 2003.Questions and feedbackWe welcome your questions, comments, and concerns about privacy. Please send us any and all feedback pertaining to privacy, or any other issue.Online Policy OnlyThis online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.Terms and ConditionsPlease also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website.Your consentBy using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.
Alkaline
CMOS & PLC
Kenwood Batteries
Motorola Batteries
Minitor Pagers
Sealed Lead Batteries
StreamLight
Thermal Imager Batteries
More Info.
